question_data = [
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Arcade Fire&#039;s &#039;The Suburbs&#039; won the Album of the Year award in the 2011 Grammys.",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Rapper Snoop Dogg&#039;s real name is &#039;Cordozar Calvin Broadus, Jr.&#039;.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Soulja Boy&#039;s &#039;Crank That&#039; won a Grammy for Best Rap Song in 2007.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Eurobeat is primarily an Italian genre of music.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Scottish producer Calvin Harris is from the town of Dumfries, Scotland.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "The song &quot;Mystery Train&quot; was released by artist &quot;Little Junior&#039;s Blue Flames&quot; in 1953.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "EDM label Monstercat signs tracks instead of artists.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "A Saxophone is a brass instrument.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "3 members of 2 Live Crew were arrested for playing songs from their album, As Nasty As They Wanna Be, live.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Stevie Wonder&#039;s real name is Stevland Hardaway Morris.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Nick Mason is the only member to appear on every Pink Floyd album.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "Pete Townshend&#039;s solo album, &quot;White City: A Novel&quot;, is set in the metropolitan area of Chicago.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Michael Jackson wrote The Simpsons song &quot;Do the Bartman&quot;.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In 1993, Prince changed his name to an unpronounceable symbol because he was unhappy with his contract with Warner Bros.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "A Facebook campaign placed Rage Against The Machine&#039;s &quot;Killing in the Name Of&quot; as the UK Christmas Number 1 in 2009.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "&quot;Neutral Milk Hotel&quot; is a real band.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Green Day&#039;s album &#039;American Idiot&#039; is considered a &quot;punk rock opera.&quot;",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
